const words = [
    {
        question: "Push The Numbers To Make A Call",
        a: "Hold On",
        b: "Dial",
        c: "Call Back",
        d: "Hang Up",
        correct: "Dial"
    },
    {
        question: "Being Used",
        a: "Dial",
        b: "Get Cut Off",
        c: "Call Back",
        d: "Engaged",
        correct: "Engaged"
    },
    {
        question: "I Like Italian Food.<br />He Said He ______ Italian Food.",
        a: "Liked",
        b: "Had Liked",
        c: "Did Like",
        d: "Has Liked",
        correct: "Liked"
    },
    {
        question: "It Was Snowing This Morning.<br />She Told Me It _______ Snowing That Morning.",
        a: "Had Been",
        b: "Has Been",
        c: "Was",
        d: "Is Going To Be",
        correct: "Had Been"
    },
    {
        question: "Could You ____ The Phone?<br />I Think Its Important.",
        a: "Pick Up",
        b: "Dial",
        c: "Call Back",
        d: "Cut Off",
        correct: "Pick Up"
    },
    {
        question: "'By the time I'm 60 you'll have grown up' - my mum said <br />His mum said he ______ by the time she's 60",
        a: "Would have grown up",
        b: "Will grow up",
        c: "Was going to grow up",
        d: "would grow up",
        correct: "Would have grown up"
    },
    {
        question: "Ile miejsc zwiedza przed koncem lata?",
        a: "How many places are they going to visit by the end of summer",
        b: "How many places will have they visited ...",
        c: "How many places will they have been visiting ...",
        d: "How many places will they have visited ...",
        correct: "How many places will they have visited ..."
    },
    {
        question: "Krotko mowiac",
        a: "being direct",
        b: "to talk briefly",
        c: "to cut a long story short",
        d: "speaking shortly",
        correct: "to cut a long story short"
    },
    {
        question: "They ____ at midnight",
        a: "will be sleeping",
        b: "will sleep",
        c: "is be sleeping",
        d: "will been sleeping",
        correct: "will be sleeping"
    },
    {
        question: "____ a horse tomorrow",
        a: "she shall have been riding",
        b: "she'll riding",
        c: "she will be riding",
        d: "she would been riding",
        correct: "she will be riding"
    },
    {
        question: "_____ the whole evening",
        a: "She will be singing",
        b: "She is going singing",
        c: "She will have been singing",
        d: "She will been sing song",
        correct: "She will be singing"
    },
    {
        question: "'I like big burgers' - he said",
        a: "He said he likes big burgers",
        b: "He told me he liked big burgers",
        c: "He said he liked big burgers",
        d: "He said he's liked big burgers",
        correct: "He said he liked big burgers"
    }
];